<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[IC Zenith Magazine]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[IC Zenith Magazine]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ic-zenith-magazine/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 09:34:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ic-zenith-magazine/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[She stopped what?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>She stopped what?</h1><p>I used to think I need to force and push myself to do my work. I thought the work is not well done if I am not exhausted after the day. I didn’t rejuvenate. Now looking back, I remember how I called "not to have too many client meetings during the day" a relaxing day. Needless to say, I didn’t have much to give to my family in the evenings and after a while, I didn’t have much to give to my clients either. I had exhausted the one and only irreplaceable resource I had; ME. </p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/81e41129-e7b1-4fca-9722-30302542a13b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ic-zenith-magazine/i-used-to-think-i-need-to-force-and-push-myself-to-do-my-wor/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">25456221-c36f-49e7-8903-8bb28ae92da5</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 09:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The entrepreneurial freedom is a real deal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The entrepreneurial freedom is a real deal</h1><p>I know for a fact, that entrepreneurial freedom is available for everyone, who embraces it and makes room for it in their life.  I live it, not yet financially free as the fashionable term goes, but as free as a bird, what comes to fulfilling my dreams and goals in business. But before that, there was some work to be done. Its your turn to tune into attitudes and core beliefs you have about working and especially about successfully working.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8e567163-959c-4219-a64b-d82e68f823f5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ic-zenith-magazine/i-know-for-a-fact-that-entrepreneurial-freedom-is-available/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dbf6f2f8-9d89-4133-9e46-7fd26b69342c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 09:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome</h1><p>There really are no words to describe how happy I am that you have found me, but I will try anyway. 
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ic-zenith-magazine/welcome/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1dcd2df5-ba76-4c4c-b48c-b78677e8b637</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 09:33:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I shall never forget the time I realised the shift from masculine energy to the feminine energy had truly happened for me. I had tried to create that shift so many times but always found myself pushing forward and forcing things to happen the way my ego would want things to happen. 

Until this one client came along. She had many things on her plate. And we had an ambitious plan to get her marketing planned to the last detail. A schedule for the “this is the way you are supposed to do things” -client meetings was hectic and massive. As you probably guessed already, it did not work out.   

You see, social media is not a cookie cutter model it is made out to be. There is not one right thing to do or one wrong thing to do. You have as many opinions about any detail about social media as you have gurus telling you how you are supposed to do it.   
And then I decided to apply to her, what I had applied to myself. 

For the first time ever, I completely stopped what we had planned for her and stepped into this divinely guided coaching process.   What came out of that, was something so beautiful, that I still get teary-eyed when I think about that. Over the years, she had accumulated a lot of unclarity in her business. A lot of strands to fog her vision. Most of which had come from the expectations placed on her by other people. And during this process, she was able to let go of her need to fulfill those expectations. From that place, she made a big transformation and started to completely immerse herself in her unique brilliance.

And it didn’t stop there, it gets better… 

As a result, she got happier, surer of herself, more self-confident and now she had the clarity on what she says yes to and more importantly what she says no to. She has more time for herself and her family and more freedom to her artistic creativity. It is like the floodgates were opened and the abundance of ideas was surging in. She has that clear vision what she wants to create and it is in the perfect alignment  with her true desires.

That (first name), is deep down what I want for you. To know how to market is really is just the icing on the cake. This was the first time I really witnessed, that creating that connection with your divine self, truly sets you free of all the other junk piling up around you in your business and personal life. It is baggage that doesn’t belong to you, so don’t take it on. </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ic-zenith-magazine/i-shall-never-forget-the-time-i-realised-the-shift-from-masc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2858d2e8-1509-4723-b66b-918fa2e37a08</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 09:33:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>